The subject of automation and its role in our economy has taken hold in American public discourse.
自动化及其在我国经济中的作用这一话题，已在美国的公共讨论中扎下根来。
Technology broadly and automation specifically are dramatically reshaping the way we work.
宽泛地说是技术，具体地说是自动化，正在极大地重塑我们的工作方式。
And we need to have a plan for what’s still to come.
而且，我们需要为今后还将发生的事情做好规划。
We don’t have to look further than our own communities to see the devastating impact of automation.
要看到自动化造成的毁灭性影响，我们只需看看自己所在的社区就够了。
From automated warehouses to cashierless grocery stores to neighborhood libraries that offer self-checkout lanes instead of employing real people—automation is increasingly replacing jobs and leaving too few good new jobs behind.
从自动化仓库到无人收银的杂货店，再到设置自助借书通道而不雇用真人的社区图书馆——自动化正越来越多地取代工作岗位，留下的优质新岗位却太少。
The statistics in manufacturing are staggering.
制造业的统计数据令人震惊。
Despite the widespread fears about trade, a recent report showed that just 13 percent of jobs lost in manufacturing are due to trade—the rest of the losses have been due to advances in technology.
尽管人们普遍对贸易心存担忧，但最近的一份报告显示，制造业流失的工作岗位中只有13%是贸易造成的——其余岗位的流失都源于技术进步。
That is why more people are criticizing the ever-increasing role of technology in our economy.
正因如此，越来越多的人对技术在我国经济中日益扩大的作用提出批评。
Our country is manufacturing more than ever before, but we are doing it with fewer workers.
我国制造的产品比以往任何时候都多，但所用的工人却更少了。
However, it’s not just factories that are seeing losses—software and information technology are also having a dramatic impact on jobs most people think are secure from the forces of a rapidly changing economy.
然而，出现岗位流失的不只是工厂——软件和信息技术也正在对一些工作岗位产生巨大影响，而大多数人认为，这些岗位不会受到快速变化的经济中各种力量的冲击。
Something transformative is happening in America that is having an adverse effect on American families.
美国正在发生一场深刻的变革，这场变革正对美国家庭产生不利影响。
Whether policymakers and politicians admit it or not, workers have made clear their feelings about their economic insecurity and desire to keep good jobs in America.
无论政策制定者和政界人士承认与否，工人们都已清楚地表明了自己对经济上缺乏保障的感受，以及让好工作留在美国的愿望。
So why are people so insistent on ignoring the perils of automation?
那么，人们为什么如此执意无视自动化的危险呢？
They are failing to look ahead at a time when planning for the future is more important than ever.
在为未来做规划比以往任何时候都更重要的当下，他们却没能向前看。
Resisting automation is futile: it is as inevitable as industrialization was before it.
抵制自动化是徒劳的：它就像此前的工业化一样不可避免。
I sincerely hope that those who assert that automation will make us more effective and pave the way for new occupations are right, but the reality of automation’s detrimental effects on workers makes me skeptical.
有些人断言，自动化会让我们更有成效，并为新的职业铺平道路，我真心希望他们是对的；但自动化对工人造成有害影响这一现实，让我心存怀疑。
No one can currently say where the new jobs are coming from or when, and any sensible company or country should prepare for all alternatives.
目前，谁也说不清新的工作岗位会从哪里来、什么时候来，任何明智的公司或国家都应该为各种可能的情况做好准备。
I’m not overstating the danger: look at what’s happened to the labor force.
我并没有夸大这种危险：看看劳动力队伍都发生了什么就知道了。
According to economic research, one in six working-age men, 25–54, doesn’t have a job.
根据经济研究，在25至54岁的劳动年龄男性中，每六人就有一人没有工作。
Fifty years ago, nearly 100 percent of men that age were working.
五十年前，这一年龄段的男性中有近100%都在工作。
Women’s labor force participation, meanwhile, has slipped back to the level it was at in the late 1980s.
与此同时，女性的劳动参与率已回落到20世纪80年代末的水平。
American families and prominent business leaders are aware that there’s a big problem with automation.
美国家庭和知名商界领袖都意识到，自动化存在一个大问题。
The value of a college degree is diminishing, and our upward mobility is declining.
大学学位的价值正在降低，我们的向上流动性也在下降。
If we want an economy that allows everyone to be economically secure, we need to start thinking about how we can rightfully address automation.
如果我们希望经济体系能让每个人都有经济保障，就需要开始思考如何正当合理地应对自动化。